search

You are here:

1. [Minecraft Servers](https://minecraft-server-list.com/) 
»2. Privacy Policy / Statement - Minecraft Server List 

Privacy Policy / Statement - Minecraft Server List
==================================================

Minecraft-server-list.com will only collect and use information from our users to be able to make a better and more reliable service for our users. All data we collect will never be shared with any third-party, but only used in-house to improve the site.

If you got any specific questions or seek more information about this, please contact us through email at admin\[@\]Minecraft-server-list.com

**Type of data our server will collect:**  
**Cookies:**  
We use cookies to store information about users, to be able to deliver users the same preferences as used on earlier visits. We record which pages users visit, IP address, browser type, time on site, referring pages. We do not publish any of this, but simply use it to improve this service.  
Cookie will also be stored if you select the “Remember me” checkbox on login. This is to store your details to keep you logged in. You can click Logout to clear this cookie.

**Statistics / Logs:**  
We use a third-party statistic modules (Google Analytics) whom also place a cookie and collect visitor data. Again these data are only avaliable to Minecraft-server-list.com and will not be shared with any third-party.

**Advertisement:**  
DoubleClick DART Cookie

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Minecraft-server-list.com
* Google.s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Minecraft-server-list.com and other sites on the Internet.
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL :: [http://www.google.com/privacy\_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

* Google Adsense

These third-party ads and statictics use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Minecraft-server-list.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies and JavaScript) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
Minecraft-server-list.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Minecraft-server-list.com.s privacy policy does not apply to these and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers. respective websites.

Privacy policies have been updated: 2020.05.01

[Privacy Policy](https://minecraft-server-list.com/privacy/ "Privacy Policy") | [About](https://minecraft-server-list.com/about-msl/ "About") | [Advertise](https://minecraft-server-list.com/advertise/ "How to Advertise your Minecraft Server") | [Terms of Use](https://minecraft-server-list.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms of Use") | [Update Log](https://minecraft-server-list.com/update-log/ "Update Log") | [Contact](https://minecraft-server-list.com/contact/ "Contact") | © Copyright 2010-2024. All Rights Reserved.  
The game Minecraft is created by Mojang AB and is not affiliated with this site.

Website created and maintained by: [Koala Designs ApS](https://www.koaladesigns.dk/ "koala designs")
